pelotoncycle.com 2017-02-24

# Peloton | Privacy Policy

Last Updated: February 11, 2016

Welcome to our Privacy Policy!

Peloton Interactive, Inc. (formerly Peloton Interactive, LLC) ("Peloton") has adopted this privacy policy to let you know how we treat the information that we collect from you, how that information is used, with whom we share it, and your choices about such uses and disclosures.  
If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please refer to the end of this Privacy Policy for information on how to contact us. 

_In General._ We collect both personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information from you as described in greater detail below. 

_Purchases._ If you choose to purchase a Peloton Bike, other Peloton products and/or other goods and services from us, including live in-studio classes or subscription services offered through any device, we may collect some or all of the following information: 

  * Full name;
  * Email address;
  * Mailing address; 
  * Phone number; and
  * Other required or optional information as may be necessary or requested. 

In addition, when you make a purchase, you may be given the opportunity to create an account with a username and password. Your username and password are personal to you and you should keep them safe and secure and not share them with anyone. 

_Live Studio._ If you choose to attend a fitness class at our live studio, we may collect some or all of the following information: 

  * Full name;
  * Email address;
  * Mailing address;
  * Phone number;
  * Emergency Contact; and
  * Other required or optional information as may be necessary or requested by Peloton. 

In addition, you may be given the opportunity to create an account with a username and password. Your username and password are personal to you and you should keep them safe and secure and not share them with anyone. 

_Financial Information._ If you choose to purchase a Peloton Bike, other Peloton products and/or other goods and services from us, including live in-studio classes or subscription services offered through any device, you may be asked to provide your payment information, such as a credit card number and/or other related information that may be required from you to complete your purchase (“Financial Information”). We do not collect, store or maintain your Financial Information, but merely provide a gateway to our third party payment processor, who will collect that information and process your payment. 

_Information you provided through Kickstarter._ We have completed our campaign through the Kickstarter web service. When you provided information through Kickstarter that information was and is subject to their collection practices and we ask that you refer to their service for information. The information you provided to them, which they provided to us, is subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

_Non-Personally Identifiable Information._ In addition to the information above, we collect certain non-personally identifiable information, which may include, but not be limited to: 

  * In-studio attendance history;
  * Purchase history;
  * Fitness related information;
  * Frequency of at home workouts;
  * Length of at home workouts; and/or
  * Other information.

_Cookies._ When you visit our website, we may assign your computer one or more cookies to facilitate access to our site and to personalize your online experience. Through the use of a cookie, we also may automatically collect information about your online activity on our site, such as the web pages you visit, the links you click, and the searches you conduct on our site. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, please note that you may not be able to sign in or use some of the interactive features offered on our website. We may also use standard Internet technology, such as web beacons and other similar technologies, to track your use of our site. 

_In general._ We may use information that we collect about you to:

  * to deliver email notifications to you about our products and services; 
  * to provide you with the products and services that you purchase from us; 
  * to enhance or supplement our service and products for you; 
  * to communicate with your regarding the status of your products and services and to allow you to communicate with us; 
  * perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our products, services, or content, or products, services or content offered by others; and 
  * perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection. 

_Personal information._ We do not share your personal information with any third parties, except as may be necessary to deliver email messages to you, provide analytics and systems analysis for our internal use, process your payment information and/or provide other products and services that you have requested from us. Notwithstanding the foregoing, from time to time we may run promotional or marketing efforts, including, but not limited to contest, sweepstakes and/or give-aways with third parties (collectively, “Promotions”). If you choose to participate in any such Promotions, then any personal information you provide in order to participate in a Promotion may be shared with such third parties and be subject to the privacy policies of those third parties. In addition, you may be provided the opportunity to share your information through third party services like Facebook and Strava, if you choose to do so. 

_Public Profiles._ You may be given the opportunity to create profile, which may include the following: 

  * User name;
  * Home city or town;
  * Image;
  * Classes taken;
  * Fitness performance history;
  * Followers;
  * Peloton achievements; and
  * Such other information as may be available from time to time. 

These profiles will be available for view by Peloton subscribers. 

_Financial Information._ As described above, we do not store, process or maintain any of your Financial Information. When you provide your Financial Information on the payment page of our web service, we pass that information directly to our third party payment processor who confirms your payment information, which then allows us to complete the transaction. 

_Other Situations._ We also may disclose your information:

  * In response to a subpoena or similar investigative demand, a court order, or a request for cooperation from a law enforcement or other government agency; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases, we may raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us. 
  * In connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of our business, a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy. 

_Unsubscribe._ If you have provided us with your email address and you would like to unsubscribe from our service, then please click on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any of our email communications. It may take up to 72 hours to process your unsubscribe request. 

_Accounts._ If you have purchased a subscription for the Peloton service or otherwise signed up for an account, then you may access your Peloton account at any time once logged onto the Peloton Bike , Peloton App or Peloton website and you may modify, update and change your account settings through your account. 

We take appropriate security measures (including physical, electronic and procedural measures) to help safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access and disclosure. For example, only authorized employees are permitted to access personal information, and they may do so only for permitted business functions. In addition, we use encryption in the transmission of your sensitive personal information between your system and ours, and we use firewalls to help prevent unauthorized persons from gaining access to your personal information. 

Our website, mobile apps and overall service are intended for a general audience, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. 

This Privacy Policy is intended to cover collection of information on our website from residents of the United States. If you are visiting our website from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. Please be assured that we seek to take reasonable steps to ensure that your privacy is protected. By using our services, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this privacy policy. 

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and services. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of this Privacy Policy. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our information-handling practices, or if you would like to request information about our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes, please contact us by email or postal mail as follows: 

Peloton Interactive, Inc.   
158 West 27th Street  
4th Floor  
New York NY 10001  
Attn: Privacy Officer

© Peloton 2012 - 2017, Peloton Interactive, Inc. All rights reserved
